Total Experience: 3 Year(s) 5 Month(s)

Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Computers]

Notice Period: 1 Month



Working as Software Engineer (Java with Angular developer), Having 3+ years of IT experience in Development.



Current Designation: Software Engineer

Current Company: NTT DATA FA Insurance Systems

Current Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Java, Angular, Spring, Hibernate, Maven, Spring Mvc

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 12-Jan-21

Last Modified: 12-Jan-21

## **Summary**

Experience in Core Java Development.

Experience in agular development.

Experience in Spring and Hibernate frameworks.

Scripting language: JavaScript, Python basics.

Exposure of SQL using PostgreSQL, Oracle11G, MySql.

Exposure of using Repository by SVN.

Exposure of Building Tool like Maven, Putty, WinScp.

Exposure of using Application Server like Apache Tomcat, WebSphere.

Basic knowledge of UNIX commands.

Basics knowledge of AWS.

# **Work Experience**

NTT DATA FA Insurance Systems as Software Engineer

Aug 2020 to Till Date

Having 3+ years of IT experience as Software Engineer. working as full stack(Angular with Java) developer.

PTM Digital connect pvt ltd as Software Engineer

Aug 2018 to Aug 2020

Modus Information Systems as Software Engineer

Apr 2016 to Jun 2017

#### **Education**

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computers) from Visveswaraiah Technological University (VTU) in 2015

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs:

java/J2EE certification

#### **IT Skills**

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
Hibernate		2020	3 Year(s) 1 Month(s)
spring boot		2020	1 Year(s) 5 Month(s)
SPRING MVC		2020	3 Year(s) 1 Month(s)
Angular		2020	1 Year(s) 5 Month(s)
JAVA		2020	3 Year(s) 9 Month(s)

# **Languages Known**

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English	Proficient			
Hindi	Beginner			
Kannada	Expert			
Telugu	Proficient			

### **Affirmative Action**

Physically Challenged: No

### **Work Authorization**

US Work Status: Need H1 Visa Countries: India,United Kingdom

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time